剧情回顾...
Previously on "Lost"...
是他们  其他人...
It was them. The Others...
你在这座岛上看见过其他人吗?
Have you seen other people on this island?
我能听到他们
I hear them.
他们就在丛林里
Out there, in the jungle.
他们在悄悄说话
They whisper.
他们袭击了我们
They've attacked us,
破坏我们  还绑架我们的人
sabotaged us, abducted us!
我们不是这岛上唯一的一群人 这我们大家都知道
We're not the only people on this island, and we all know it!
也许现在我们应该停止互相责备
Maybe it's time we stopped blaming us
开始考虑一下他们了
and started worrying about them!
他们第一晚来  带走了我们三个人
They came the first night, took three of us,
后来他们又回来带走了另外九个人
then they came back and took nine more.
他们很聪明  而且像野兽一般
They're smart, and they're animals,
他们可以在任何时候出现在任何地方
and they could be anywhere at anytime,
如果你以为一把枪和一颗子弹
and if you think that one gun and one bullet
就可以阻止他们...
is gonna stop them...
再想想吧
think again
Shannon
这不是你们的岛
This is not your island.
这是我们的岛
This is our island,
你们之所以能生活在这里
and the only reason you're livin' on it
是因为我们允许你们这么做
is 'cause we let you live on it.
他们离这越来越近了  赶快撤
They're getting closer! Move it!
把它们烧了
Burn those!
再碎得快点
Shred faster!
快
Hurry up!
Sayid  把这些文件拿走
Sayid! Take these files!
烧了它们
Burn them!
你们这些孬种  继续碎文件
Keep shredding you cowards!
等我说了才能离开
We leave when I say!
再停下来  我就亲自杀了你
Stop again,and I'll kill you myself!
我是你的上级  你应该照着我的话...
I'm your commanding,officer, and you will do...
停下  趴下  快给我趴下  趴下  趴下
Stop! Get down!Get the hell down! Get down, get down!
你  不  不  不  赶紧把枪扔在地上
You, no, no, no, drop your gun on the ground now!
别动  趴在地上
Freeze! On the ground now!
不要再烧了  给我趴下
Stop burning that stuff! Get the hell down!
这儿谁指挥?
Who's in charge here?
我说这儿谁指挥?
I said who's in charge?!
最好有人告诉他停下  不然他就死定了
Somebody better tell him to stop, or god help me, he's dead!
他们听不懂  中士
They don't understand, Sergeant.
他们听的懂  听着
They understand. Listen up.
数三下我就开枪
I'll fire on three.
一  二...
One, two...
快别再碎文件了  不然他会杀了你
你
You.
你是头儿?
You in charge?
不  我不是
No, I am not.
谁是?
Who is?
我们这没有指挥官
There is no commanding officer here.
他两个小时前去了希拉
He left two hours ago for Hillah.
你的英语说得不错  阿拉伯人
Your English is good, Abdul.
但是你在撒谎
But you're lying.
这可不好
And that ain't so good.
就是他  中士
That's him, Sergeant.
我们走  伙计
Let's go, hombre.
小子  我们和你一样也不想待在这儿
Son, we don't wanna be here any more than you do,
但是你们的兄弟萨达姆打到了科威特
but your pal Saddam had to go marching into Kuwait.
所以我们来了
Here we all are.
听Buccelli说你会说英语
Buccelli here says you speak English.
你做过翻译么?
You ever do any translating?
正式的?  没有
Formally, no.
靠
Hell.
你还知道"正式的"是什么意思
Fact that you know what "formally" means...
那就没问题了
We're good.
两天前我们有一架阿帕奇直升机 在这个地区坠毁了
Apache helicopter went down in this sector two days ago.
我们的情报显示飞行员被抓了
Our sources tell us the pilot was captured.
救回这个飞行员对于我们来说很重要
It's very important that we get this pilot back.
我们知道他被带到了当地的 共和国卫队情报首长那里...
He was taken to the Republican Guard intelligence commander,
一个叫Tariq的人
a man named Tariq.
你认不认识?
Do you know him?
认识  他就是我们的指挥官
Yes. He was our commanding officer.
你知道他在哪?
Do you know where he is?
轰炸开始的时候
When the bombing started,
他就逃到了希拉
he fled to Hillah.
希拉  是么?
Hillah, huh?
对  没错
Yes, that is right.
那就欢迎来到希拉
Welcome to Hillah.
Jack在哪?
Where's Jack?
怎么了?
Why?
那儿
There.
看见了吗?
See?
回去  这儿由我来应付
Go back. I'll deal with this.
什么?
What?
回去  Ana Lucia
Go back, Ana Lucia.
别告诉任何人你看到了什么
And don't tell anyone what you saw.
你在这儿干什么  Danielle?
What are you doing here, Danielle?
我在找你
Looking for you.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
我们这是去哪?
Where are we going?
你说你在找我
You said you were looking for me.
你是怎么想的...
What was your plan?
躲在树丛里
To hide in the woods,
希望我会路过?
hoping I would pass you by?
我想等天黑了
I was going to wait until dark,
再去你的帐篷找你
and then find you at your tent.
为什么?
Why?
我们得一直走
We need to keep moving.
除非你先告诉我去哪儿
Tell me where we are moving to.
相信我
Trust me.
我们上一次见面的时候
The last time we met,
你警告我们其他人要来了
you warned us the Others were coming,
结果他们没来
which they weren't.
实际上  你是为了引开我们的注意力 好掳走Claire的孩子
In fact, it was a diversion to kidnap Claire's baby.
所以很抱歉  我不能相信你
So pardon me for not trusting you.
我带你去的地方...
This place I am taking you to,
那里有东西可以帮助你
there is something that will help you,
一些很重要的东西
something important.
所以相信我
As for trust,
拿着这个
take this.
如果我骗你 你就开枪好了
If I'm lying, it's yours to use.
还有多远?
How much further?
不远了
Not far.
问他飞行员被带到哪里去了
Ask him where he took the pilot.
他们想知道飞行员在哪里
告诉他他妈是色鬼
他说他不知道
He says he does not know.
听着  我们知道他前天 审问了那个飞行员...
We know for a fact he interrogated the pilot day before yesterday.
而且可能就是在这个房间
Hell, probably in this room.
告诉他
Tell him,
只要我们的人完好无损的回来 他就自由了
we get our man back safe and sound,he goes free.
如果你告诉他们飞行员在哪里 他们就让你走
你真是无耻
你是个伊拉克士兵
偷走他的枪  把他们都杀了
枪就在他的皮带上
你死前至少可以杀掉他们好几个
他在说什么?
What's he saying?
他说他不知道
He says he does not know.
我可不是一岁的小孩了
I was born,but I wasn't born yesterday, son.
你不肯帮忙  自然有别人会来接替
You don't help me out here,someone else will take over,
而那个人
and that someone,
他才不会心软呢
he won't play nice at all.
对不起
I am sorry.
他不知道
He does not know.
好吧  你是有过机会的
OK. You had your chance.
卫兵
Guards.
把他关起来
Lock him back up.
真不可思议
This is unbelievable.
嘿  嘿  你听见没有?
Hey. Hey, you hear that thing?
你听见那只青蛙了吗?
You hear that frog?
青蛙?
Frog?
帮我一起去找找看?
You wanna help me find it?
怎么着  我们不再是朋友了?
What? We ain't friends anymore?
你在干什么?
What you got there, Rerun?
没什么
Nothing.
没错  不过你的脸上还有一块叫 "没什么"的东西
Yeah, well, you got a spot of nothing on your chin there.
"达摩启动计划奶油色拉酱"
Dharma Initiative Ranch Dressing?
你知道  打开它后应该把它放冰箱里
You're supposed to refrigerate that after you open it.
事实上  这背面写着
Actually, on the back it says
它可以在室温下保存七年
it'll keep at room temperature for up to seven years.
哟  看看是谁的私人储藏室
Well, well.Looky who's got a secret stash.
别  伙计  你可不能说
Please, dude. You can't tell.
什么  不说你从大伙那偷东西吃?
What? That you stole food from the group?
我为什么不说呢?
Now, why would I wanna do that?
嗨  伙计  拜托了好不好?
Come on, man. Please.
可恶的东西
Son of a bitch.
伙计  只是只树蛙而以
Dude, it's just a tree frog.
你见过?
Have you seen it?
是啊
Yeah.
我和你说
Tell you what,
你帮我找到它 就可以安心继续享受你的色拉
you help me find that thing,you can keep right on Ranch dipping.
说定了?
We got a deal?
还有多远?
How much further?
Danielle?
我们到了
We're here.
这里到底是哪儿啊?
And where exactly is "here"?
那些拿来干嘛  Danielle?
What is that for, Danielle?
救命
Help me!
这儿
Hey! Over here!
等等
Wait.
Sayid  听我的
Sayid, listen to me.
在这儿
Over here!
求求你  救救我
Please! Help me!
救命
Help me!
千万别信他说的
Don't believe a word he says.
他是他们中的一个
He's one of them.
我一点也不知道她在说什么
I have no idea what she's talking about.
她疯了
She's crazy.
他在那上边多久了?
How long has he been up there?
昨晚开始
Since last night.
求求你  把我放下来
Please just cut me down.
我叫Henry Gale
My name is Henry Gale.
我来自明尼苏达
I'm from Minnesota.
求求你
Please.
他在说谎
He's lying.
我要把他放下来
I'm going to cut him down.
别
Don't.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你犯了个严重的错误
You're making a serious mistake.
没事了  没事了  你没事了
It's OK. It's OK.You're all right.
你没事了
You're all right.
等等
Hold on.
别紧张
Take it easy.
哦  不
No.
等等
Wait.
Danielle  别
Danielle, don't.
你会杀了他
You could have killed him.
如果我想杀他  他早就死了
If I wanted to kill him,I would have killed him.
你无缘无故射了这个人
You shot this man with no provocation.
他是他们中的一个
He is one of them.
把他绑起来
Tie him up.
你应该带他去见你们的医生
You should take him to your doctor.
他死了就没用了
He's no good to you dead.
然后怎么样呢?
And then what?
你问他话  Sayid
You'll talk to him, Sayid.
没记错的话
As I recall,
这是你的老本行
that is what you do.
但是记住...
But know this:
他会说谎的
He will lie.
很长一段时间
For a long time,
他会不停说慌
he will lie.
我想和你谈谈你的朋友
I wanna talk to you about your buddy,
Tariq
好吧  我了解
Ah, look, I get it.
你是个忠诚的人
You're a man who values loyalty.
甚至为我们做翻译都觉得 好像在做什么错事
Even doing a little translating for us,you feel like you're doing the wrong thing.
我了解
I get that,
也尊重你
and I respect it.
这是Tariq在掌管你的情报部门前 所作的事情
This is what Tariq was doing before he took over command of your intelligence unit.
他曾经是北方一支化学战队的指挥官
He was the head of a chemical warfare battalion in the north.
曾亲自监督了这个村庄里 沙林毒气的使用
Personally supervised the use of sarin gas on this village.
你认识这个村子  对吧?
You recognize it, don't you?
你在那个村子有亲戚  对吧  Sayid?
You had relatives in that village didn't you, Sayid?
你知道沙林毒气能造成什么后果
So, you know what sarin gas does.
无论男女老少
No discrimination.
整个集市
The entire marketplace.
无辜的妇女...
Innocent women,
孩子
children.
够了...
Enough.
拜托
Please.
忠诚是美德
Loyalty is a virtue.
但是无条件的忠诚...
But unquestioning loyalty...
我觉得你不会是这样的
I don't think that's you.
我为什么要相信你?
Why should I believe you?
你觉得我们怎么知道 你在那个村子有亲戚的?
How do you think we knew you had relatives in that village?
我们获得了你和Tariq的个人档案
We liberated your personnel file and Tariq's.
我们只想救回我们的飞行员
All we want is our pilot back,
然后把他送回家跟家人团聚
so we can send him home to his family.
Tariq不会告诉你们的
Tariq will never talk to you.
这就是为什么你必须要让他告诉你
That's why you're gonna have to make him talk to you.
John  John  醒醒
John. John, wake up.
怎么了?
What?
出来一下
Come out here.
明尼苏达  是么?
Minnesota, huh?
很可疑  不是么?
That's the question, isn't it?
这是...这是在哪儿?
Wh... Where am I?
你是谁?
Who are you?
Henry  Henry Gale
我的背
Ah, my back.
我们会把它取出来 但是首先你得放松
We're going to take it out,but first I want you to relax.
你怎么到这个岛上的?
How did you get to this island?
四个月前
Four months ago.
我们掉到这个岛上  我妻子和我
We crashed, my wife and I.
什么坠毁了?
Crashed in what?
一个热气球
A balloon.
我们正尝试横穿太平洋
We were trying to cross the Pacific.
你的妻子...她在哪儿?
Your wife, where is she?
她死了
She died.
她...
She got...
三个星期前生了病
She got sick, three weeks ago.
我们呆在沙滩那边的一个洞穴里
We were staying in a cave off the beach.
我的肩膀
My shoulder.
至少给我的胳膊松绑
At least untie my arms.
这儿怎么了?
What the hell's going on here?
Rousseau把他困在了丛林里
Rousseau trapped him in the jungle.
她认为他是"其他人"
She believes he's an Other.
其他人?
Another what?
你用箭射他?
You shot him with an arrow?
我有弓吗?
Do I have a bow?
能听见我说么?
Hey, hey. You with me?
你准备让他流血至死?
You were gonna let him bleed to death?
我只是想趁着他还行的时候 从他嘴里得到真实可靠的回答
I was trying to get honest answers.
他的伤根本不致命
And his wound is far from life-threatening.
我们应该让Jack先治疗他  然后再问我们想知道的东西
We should let Jack treat him first.Then we'll get our answers.
Jack...
别把绳子松开
Do not untie him.
恐怖片里的人就是这么被弄死的
This is how people get killed in scary movies.
如果这是恐怖片  我应该是和一个 美女在一起  而不是你
If this were a scary movie, I'd be with a hot chick, not you, Barbar.
我怎么了
It's Babar.
你好闭嘴了
Why don't you shut up, Hammo?
不然你的色拉紊乱症立马成为椰子岛互联网上新的头条了
Or your Ranch disorder's gonna be the new lead item on the coconut internet.
好吧
Fine.
随你便
Go ahead.
告诉所有人那个胖子 一直在私藏奶油色拉酱
Tell everyone the fat guy's been hiding Ranch dressing.
那个喜欢吃的胖子
The fat guy likes to eat.
对  我很胖
Yeah, I'm fat.
胖  胖  胖  胖  胖
Fat, fat, fat, fat, fat.
你以为我不知道么?
You think I don't know that?
至少人们喜欢我
At least people like me.
你知道吗? 你自己去找那该死的青蛙吧
Well, find the damn frog by yourself.
Hurley  等等
Hurley, wait.
等等  嘿  Hurley
Wait. Hey, Hurley.
听着  伙计  对不起  好了吧?
Look, man, I'm sorry. All right?
那个青蛙快要折磨死我了
But this frog is killing me.
你得帮帮我...
You gotta help me out.
求你了
Please.
你怎么看?
So, what do you think?
你怎么认为  John?
What do you think, John?
我觉得他很有说服力
I think he's pretty convincing.
没错
Yes, he is.
问题是我们没办法
The real problem is there's no way
确定他是在说实话
we can be sure he's telling the truth.
那可不一定
That is not necessarily true.
Jack是不是有武器库的密码?
Does Jack have the combination to the armory?
现在是这样
For now he does.
你改密码要花多长时间?
How long would it take for you to change it?
如果你很生气
If you're angry,
想找个人来出出气...
looking for someone to punish...
我为什么要找人出气?
Why would I need to punish anyone?
我想要知道他到底是谁
I want to find out who he is.
我想要知道真相
I want the truth.
我想我们都知道Jack肯定会采取一些措施
We both know that Jack will have issues with what must be done to get it.
所以要多久  John
So, how long, John,
能改掉密码?
to change the combination?
最多几分钟
Couple of minutes, tops.
那我建议你现在就开始
Then I suggest you get started.
-在你治疗的时候他有没有说...  -没有
-Did he say anything while...  -No, he didn't.
他休克了
He was in shock.
我们不能让他这么躺着  Jack
We can't just leave him laying here,Jack.
人们会看见他  接着恐慌就会开始了
People will see him.It'll create a panic.
是么?  那你觉得我们应该把他放哪?
Where do you think we should put him?
不如把他放在武器库里
I say we put him in the armory.
那里很安全
It's secure.
为了大家安全 就算犯个错也是值得的  Jack
Better to err on the side of safety,Jack,
至少等到我们确定他是好人
at least until we can be sure.
好吧
OK.
暂时先这样
For now.
好  把那个帆布床拖进来
We can pull that cot in here.
他背上有伤  不能直接这么躺着
He shouldn't be on his back.
好主意
Good idea.
Sayid
你到底是在干嘛?
Hey. What the hell are you doing?
Sayid
做应该做的
What needs to be done.
他们让你单独和我谈吗?
They're letting speak to me alone now?
你得告诉我那个飞行员在哪儿
You need to tell me where the helicopter pilot is.
这就是他们的新把戏?
This is their new bluff?
让你来拷问我?
That you're going to torture me?
他们觉得你会这么做?
They think you will do this?
Sayid  你是一名忠诚的士兵
Sayid, you are a loyal soldier.
一个伟大英雄的儿子
The son of a great hero.
别让你的父亲蒙羞
Do not disgrace your father!
你不敢碰我的
You wouldn't dare harm me!
你要听我的命令  我是指挥官
You will follow my orders as your commanding officer!
拿着那个袋子
Take that bag.
罩在你的头上再用带子绑起来
Put it over your head and tape it up.
现在就杀了你自己
Kill yourself, now!
这是命令
That's an order.
照做  然后带着你仅剩的一点荣誉死去吧
Do it and die with what little honor you have left.
你让我自杀...
You would have me take my own life...
这对你毫无意义
the information means nothing to you!
那个飞行员两天前就被处决了
The pilot was executed two days ago.
他被埋在四公里外的一块地里
He is buried in a field four kilometers from here.
我可以带你去那儿
I can take you there.
可恶
Damn it.
Sayid  开门
Sayid, open the door.
Sayid  回答我
Sayid, answer me.
Jack
这密码怎么不行  John?
Why isn't this combination working,John?
你改过了?
Did you change it?
是的
Yeah.
你为什么这么做?
Why would you do that?
你在组建军队
You're raising an army.
什么?
What?
你为什么没要我帮忙? 当然  这是你的事
Why you didn't ask me is your business.
但要组建军队只可能有一个理由  Jack
But there's only one reason to raise an army,
那就是因为我们面临战争
and that's because we're at war.
不管你喜不喜欢
And like it or not,
Sayid在这门后做的任何事 也是这场战争的一部分
whatever Sayid has to do behind that door,that's a part of it, too.
如果他说的是实话呢  John?
What if he's telling the truth, John?
如果不是呢?
What if he's not?
起来
Get up.
发...发生了什么事?
What's happening?
来  让我帮你一把
Here. Let me help you.
你说你在这岛上已经四个月了
You said you've been here for four months.
你说你四个月前到的这个岛上  对吧?
You said you came to this island four months ago, yes?
我在哪?
Where am I?
我叫你
Please.
回答我的问题
Answer my question.
对...对  我们四个月前落在了岛上
Yeah, yes. We landed four months ago.
可能还不止四个月
Maybe more.
你一直呆在一个洞里?
You were in a cave for all that time?
在沙滩那边...
Off the beach.
这个岛的北岸
On the north shore of the island.
从那片沙滩到你被抓住的地方有多远?
How far from where you were captured?
我不知道
I don't know.
-几天的路程?  -两...两天
-How many days walk?  -Two. Two days.
你们为什么要呆在沙滩上那么长时间?
Why did you stay on the beach so long?
为什么不呢?
Why wouldn't we?
我们希望能等到低空飞行的飞机
We wanted to be there for flyovers.
我们有一个信号发射器
We had an emergency beacon,a transmitter.
什么样的发射器?
What kind of transmitter?
一个标准式样的
An ADF beacon.
我们想确定我们能被雷达发现
We wanted to make sure we'd be spotted.
听着
Look,
无论你认为我是谁  我不是
whatever you think I am, I'm not.
拜托  拜托...
Please, please,
你叫什么?
just tell me your name.
你妻子...她原来姓什么?
Your wife. What is her maiden name?
-Murphy  -你在哪儿认识她的?
-Murphy.  -Where did you meet her?
明尼苏达大学
University of Minnesota.
她是怎么死的?
How did she die?
她病死的
She got sick.
生病了?
She got sick?
一开始是发烧
It started as a fever.
两天后就神志不清...
After two days, she was delirious.
然后死了
Then she died.
我不知道你为什么问我这么多问题
I don't know why you're asking these questions.
我也不明白你为何这样对我...
I don't know why you're treating me this way,
为什么我必须向你解释我是谁
why I have to explain to you who I am
而你却不告诉我你是谁
when you don't tell me who you are.
我23岁时  美国人来到了我们国家
I was 23 years old when the Americans came to my country.
我是一个好人
I was a good man.
我是一个士兵...
I was a soldier.
那些美国人走了之后
And when they left,
我变得跟以前不同了
I was something different.
在之后的六年中
For the next six years
我做了许多难堪回首的事
I did things I wish I could erase from my memory,
我从来就没有想过可以做到的事...
things which I never thought myself to be capable of.
但是我却学会了...
But I did come to learn this.
我有这潜力
There is a part of me which was always capable.
你想知道我是谁?
You want to know who I am.
我叫Sayid Jarrah...
My name is Sayid Jarrah,
我是一个拷问官
and I am a torturer.
在哪儿啊?
Where is it?
在这里
There it is.
抓到了
Gotcha.
伙计  好身手
Dude, nice catch.
就算我该死
Well, I'll be damned.
这吵人的声音都是这家伙搞出来的
All that noise from this tiny critter.
它让我想起了以前我有过的一只乌龟
Kind of reminds me of a turtle I once had.
它叫Stewart
His name was Stewart.
当我十岁时它就跑掉了
He ran off when I was ten.
这些都是我妈妈说的
Well, that's what Mom said.
我有点觉得是妈妈把它扔掉的
I kind of think she threw him out.
呃  你是个快乐的小家伙  不是吗?
Wow, you're a happy little fellow,ain't you?
我有一个主意
I have an idea.
不如把它交给我吧
Why don't I take him far from here?
我把它带到两个海滩之外?
Two beaches away.
也许我会找到树蛙女士
Maybe he'll find a Mrs. Tree Frog.
这样它就不会叫了  大家都开心
That way he won't keep you up anymore and everyone's happy.
是啊  这是个办法
Yeah, that's one idea.
而这是另一个办法
Here's another.
伙计...
Dude.
我听说抹上一点色拉酱 它尝起来就像鸡肉
I hear with a little Ranch they taste just like chicken.
需要帮忙吗?
Give you a hand?
闭嘴
Shut up.
钳子到哪里去了?
Where are the pliers?
给我说说那个热气球
Tell me about this balloon.
什么?
What?
那个把你和你妻子带到这儿来的气球  跟我说说
This balloon that brought you here.Tell me about it.
你想知道什么?
What do you wanna know?
任何东西
Everything.
它高140英尺  宽60英尺...
She's 140 feet high, 60 feet wide.
在空中时  55万立方的氦和 10万立方的热空气能让它保持飞行
And when she's up in the air,550,000 cubic feet of helium and 100,000 of hot air keep her up.
如果你在空中从上往下看它
And if you could look down on her,
你可以看见在顶端有个很大的黄色笑脸
you'd see a big yellow smiley face on top.
你们为什么以这样的方式旅行呢?
Why would you travel in that way?
因为我很富有...
Because I was rich.
而且它是我的梦想...
Because it was my dream.
Jennifer也觉得这是很酷的事
And Jennifer thought it would be neat.
你很有钱?
You were rich.
我想我现在已经开始用过去的思维看待事情了
I guess I'm thinking of things in the past tense now.
很乐观吧?
How's that for optimism?
你是怎么变得那么有钱的?
What did you do to become so rich?
我卖掉我的公司
I sold my company.
什么样的公司?
What kind of company?
-矿业公司  -你们采什么矿?
-Mining.  -What did you mine?
非机械金属
We mined nonmetallic minerals.
我知道在鸡尾酒舞会上每个人都想和我说话
I know. Everyone wanted to talk to me at cocktail parties.
把你的手给我
Give me your hands.
她埋在哪儿?
Where is she buried?
-什么?  -听着
-What?  -Listen to me.
你说你埋了你的妻子  告诉我在哪里
You said you buried your wife.Tell me where.
你想干什...
What are you...
-在哪儿? -丛林里
-Where?  -In the jungle.
热气球旁边  就在丛林里
By the balloon. In the jungle.
有多深?  你挖的坟墓有多深?
How deep?How deep did you dig the grave?
我不知...
I don't...
有多深?  有多少泥土?
How many shovelfuls of earth?
你是用手吗?  挖了多久?
Did you use your hands?How long did it take you?
-我记不起来了  -你记得起来的
-I don't remember.  -You would remember.
你会记得有多深
You would remember how deep.
你应该记得那时的每铲土
You would remember every shovelful,every moment.
你应该记得把一具尸体放进去时的感觉
You would remember what it felt like to place her body inside.
如果那个被埋的是你所爱的女人 你肯定会记得的
You would remember if you buried the woman you loved.
如果这些都是真的  你会记得的
You would remember if it were true.
那你...那你是不是也失去过谁?
Did you lose someone?
你是不是在这岛上失去了谁?
Did you lose someone here on the island?
你是不是也失去过谁?
Did you lose someone, too?
她怎么了?
What happened to her?
那是一场意外
It was an accident.
杀她的那个女弄错了
The woman responsible thought she was someone else,
以为她是去害她的
someone coming to hurt her,
就像你这样的人
someone like you.
这...这...都是误会
Just, just... This is all a mistake.
我们慢慢谈  好吗?
Slow down here, OK?
伤害我也不能让她起死回生
Hurting me isn't gonna bring her back.
你知道我所失去的吧
You know what I lost.
告诉我事实
Tell me the truth.
告诉我你到底是谁
Tell me who you are.
不不不  救命  停下
No, no, no. Help. Stop.
告诉我真相  告诉我你是谁
Tell me the truth.Tell me who you are.
Sayid
Jack
打开  马上打开
Open it.Open it now, John.
Jack  这是不得已的事
This has to happen.
打开门  听见了没?
You open that damn door,you understand me?
马上打开
You open it now.
不
No.
马上
Now.
你想要我说什么?
What do you want me to say?
你现在让我干什么  我都照做
Whatever you want me to do, I'll do it.
只是拜托你...
Just, please...
我想要你告诉我真相
I want you to tell me the truth.
把门打开
Open the door.
-放开我  Jack  -不放怎样?
-Let go of me, Jack.  -Or what?
你想按按键?  打开门
Wanna push the button?Open the door.
只剩一分钟了John  你最好考虑快点
It's under a minute now, John.You better think fast.
-你不会的  -什么?
-You wouldn't.  -What?
我不会什么?
I wouldn't what?
如果我没...你想拿大家的命赌博?
If we don't...You would risk everyone's lives?
上次是你说服我按按键的  John
You talked me into pushing that button once, John,
但是现在我说你
but it's yours now.
你是那个不肯冒一下险的人  你
You're the one who won't risk it. You.
我?  我觉得它到了零什么事也不会发生
I don't think anything's gonna happen when we get to zero.
-Jack...  -你想看看会发生什么事吗?
-Jack.  -You wanna see?
那我们就来看看将会发生什么
Let's just see what's gonna happen.
你是谁?
Who are you?
好吧  好吧  好吧  右15  左...
OK, OK, OK. Right 15, left...
你当我傻么?  你去开
You think I'm stupid? You open it.
-他在撒谎 -没有
-He's lying.  -Not like this!
我会告诉你你想知道的
I'll tell you whatever you want.
他在说谎  他在说谎
He's lying! He's lying!
够了
That's enough!
到底想怎样?
What the hell was that?
他是他们中的一个
He is one of them.
他说了没?
Did he tell you that?
那你怎么知道?
Then how do you know?
因为我知道
Because I know.
他是他们其中一个
He is one of them.
Rousseau当初也是这么认为你的吧  Sayid
I think that's what Rousseau thought about you once, Sayid.
没记错的话  她设了陷阱把你捆住 而且用电击你
She strapped you down, she shocked you,
都是因为她认为你是他们中的一个
all because she thought you were one of them.
他是的
He is.
什么?
What?
他是他们中的一个
He is one of them.
对Rousseau来说  我们都是其他人
To Rousseau, we're all Others.
我想这都是相对而言的  是么
I guess it's all relative, huh?
你有妻子么?
You got a wife?
孩子?
Kids?
我来
I'll take him.
结束了  我们不去巴格达了
It's over. We're pulling out,not going to Baghdad.
你们的领袖萨达姆仍旧可以掌握政权 也就是说
Your man Saddam gets to stay in power,
你几乎肯定将继续为他效力
which means you, in all likelihood,will remain in his employ.
而且你还掌握拷问技能
I guess you're lucky you have a new skill set you can use.
你让我做的那些事...
What you made me do, no human being
人类之间不能这么做
should ever have to do to another.
将来....
One of these days...
你会想明白的
there will be something you need to know.
但是现在...
And now...
你知道怎么去得到你想知道的了
you know how to get it.
我不会再这么做了
I will never do that again.
好吧
Yeah.
祝你好运  Sayid
Good luck to you, Sayid.
给你回拉马蒂的车费
Bus fare back to Ramadi.
我们出发
Let's move out.
舱里有一个人...
There is a man down in the hatch.
Rousseau抓住的一个陌生人
A stranger captured by Rousseau.
我打了他
I beat him.
我狠狠打了他
I beat him badly.
为什么告诉我这些  Sayid?
Why are you telling me this, Sayid?
Jack问我怎么知道...
Jack asked me how I knew,
这个人在撒谎
knew for sure that this man was lying,
我怎么知道他是其他人中的一个
how I knew for sure that he was one of them, one of the Others.
我知道是因为我这么对他我一点也没内疚感
I know because I feel no guilt for what I did to him.
但是这是我对Jack甚至是Lock解释不清的...
But there is no way I can ever explain that to Jack, or even Locke,
因为他们两个都已经忘记了
because both of them have forgotten.
忘记了?  什么?
Forgotten? What?
你被吊着脖子挂在树上留着等死
That you were strung up by your neck and left for dead.
Claire被绑架了好几天 没人知道在她身上发生了什么
That Claire was kept for days during which God knows what happened to her.
这些人
That these people,
这些"其他人"
these Others,
是多么无情...
are merciless
他们可以在任何时候 带走我们中的任何一个
and can take any one of us whenever they choose.
所以告诉我  Charlie
So, tell me, Charlie,
你忘记了么?
have you forgotten?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====